f1i.com 2002-12-10

# PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY POLICY  
**  
Welcome to F1i.com, the insider's line. We will offer you the best in Formula 1 racing and we encourage you to share with us your thoughts and passions for the cars you drive - or aspire to drive. None of this information will be shared with others without your express permission.

We believe in your right to privacy. F1i.com wants to be your forum through which to discuss your obsession for automobiles. This is important for F1i.com and you. The more we understand your interests in our content, the more interesting we can make it for you.

Through its relationships in the automotive world, F1i.com will enable you access to the top designers and engineers involved in building the cars of tomorrow. You will have opportunities to contribute your thoughts on the design of fine cars to those individuals directly involved in producing them. By stating your opinions in this way, you will effectively become a member of the design teams of those car manufacturers who not only strive for bragging rights on the racecourse and on the street - but who also listen to their informed drivers.

The information you are providing will not be used in any manner to violate your trust. The information you provide will only be used to make your experience - and that of your fellow Formula 1 and automobile enthusiasts richer and more interesting. F1i.com respects your privacy and would never allow unrestricted access to your private information.

With cookie technology, we are able to greet members and recognize F1i.com insiders each time you return. Your personal information will be stored with us and kept private. Akin to the doorman at your favorite nightspot or a personal butler who knows your habits and desires to help you enjoy the experience quickly and painlessly, F1i.com will utilize this technology to build a better destination - where you can better enjoy Formula 1 racing.

 **FULL PRIVACY POLICY  
**  
Welcome to F1i.comTM! Your personal privacy and comfort are of the utmost importance to us. That's why we've taken care to provide you with the details on our information gathering and dissemination practices. Please note: this policy is applicable to the F1i.com site only. Should you leave our site through a link provided by our editors, advertisers or vendors, you should always check each site's privacy policy, as it may differ from our own. 

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

  * Information We Gather and Track
  * IP Addresses and Cookies
  * Providing Personal Information
  * How We Use Your Information
  * Your Security
  * Links to External Sites
  * Opting Out and Changing Your Personal Information
  * Our Kids Policy
  * User Agreement
  * Contact Information

**INFORMATION WE GATHER AND TRACK**

F1i.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. F1i.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**

F1i.com uses IP addresses to ascertain when a unique visitor is on our site, to identify problems with our server, and to maintain and administer our Web site. In addition, we track the URL of the last Web site you visited before accessing F1i.com and the URL you went to upon exiting our site. 

We use cookies to customize your experience on our site so that it's compatible with your operating system, and to provide you with content tailored to your specific interests. For example, if you visit featured stories about interactive Formula 1 circuit experiences, we might also advise you of products, games, or new information that allow you to virtually participate in Grand Prix races. Your cookie is only stored on your own machine, does not contain personal data, address or credit card information, and is shared only with those vendors with whom you place an order. If you choose to, you may usually disable cookies on your browser, but please note that without cookies enabled, you may be unable to make use of certain features on our site, and we will be unable to optimally customize your experience.

**PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION** **

Registration Information:

**  
You can visit our site, read our featured stories, news articles, and other materials, and check on e-commerce offerings without providing us with any personal information. However, if you wish to participate in online discussion forums (bulletin boards), you must register on the site and YOU MUST BE 16 YEARS OLD OR OVER. Please note: Any information that you choose to post on the F1i.com bulletin boards is considered public information and users should exercise caution before deciding to disclose personal information there.

**Billing Information:**  
If you wish to purchase any merchandise or make travel arrangements while on the F1i.com site, you will be required to provide specific personal information, such as your full name, billing address, credit card number and corresponding expiration date, in order to proceed. This information will be stored and transmitted in keeping with our Security policy. For more information, see the "Your Security" section below. 

**General Information:**  
Periodically, we may provide you with the opportunity to enter contests or sweepstakes, participate in polls, or complete surveys online. As your participation in these offerings is completely voluntary you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. While polls are anonymous, most surveys are not and you may be asked to provide contact or unique identifying information to increase the value of the results. You will also be required to provide personal information when entering contests or sweepstakes so that we may contact you if you are a winner.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

**Notification and Promotion:**  
General personal information you provide, such as e-mail address, full name, street address, telephone number, hobbies or interests, favorite F1 Team, type of car you drive, or any other information will be available to F1i.com", and may be available to our advertisers, vendors and promotional partners, who have been prescreened. We may use your personal information to notify you of other publications, products or services offered by F1i.com, our affiliates, vendors or promotional partners, which might be of interest to you. If at any time you do not wish to receive such communications from F1i.com, you may choose to opt-out. See the "Opting Out and Changing Your Personal Information" section below for details.   
Your personal information will also be used to contact you in response to questions you submit via email; to advise you of administrative or other issues related to the F1i.com site; to provide you with notices about new products or services available from F1i.com, our vendors, advertisers and affiliates; and to fill your orders. Your personal preferences or usage history may result in your being presented with special screens, products or services. 

**Processing Transactions:**  
If you purchase anything from our participating vendors, F1i.com and the vendor involved will maintain information about your transactions. We will also provide anonymous aggregate information about online transactions at this site to all of our advertisers, vendors and affiliates.

**Aggregate Reporting:**  
We produce aggregate reports for partners and advertisers. For example, we tell advertisers how many people saw or clicked on an ad and additionally, how many people saw or clicked on ads in different portions of our service. Where available, we may offer additional information about viewer characteristics. However this does not include personally identifiable information about you or your online usage patterns.

**Suggestions and Feedback:**  
Your suggestions and feedback, received via email or on our bulletin boards, are used to evaluate new informational features, products and services which might be of interest to our visitors; to track technical or other problems with the site; and to assess your satisfaction with our vendors and partners.

**Newsletters:**  
We use your email contact information to provide you with newsletter subscriptions, to which you may unsubscribe, or similar information we think you may find of interest. You can choose to opt out of these mailings at any time. See the "Opting Out and Changing Your Personal Information" section below for details.

**YOUR SECURITY** ****F1i.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and off-line.

**Online Security**  
Whenever one of our registration or order forms asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

Offline Security  
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

**LINKS TO EXTERNAL SITES**

F1i.com may offer links to other sites so that you can conveniently access relevant content and visit our vendors and advertisers. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We urge you to inquire about the privacy policy of any Web site before providing any personally identifiable information. 

**OPTING OUT AND CHANGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Information provided at the time of Registration or submission from a user who is 13 years of age or over may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by F1i.com and our affiliates and / or companies, which have been prescreened by F1i.com. We provide visitors the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications that are not directly related to our site when we first request registration or order information.

After you've chosen to opt out, we will do our best to ensure that you do not receive additional messages or information from us, but are not responsible for further contacts that derive from activities to which you previously consented. Any information previously given to our vendors, advertisers and others cannot be rescinded. We may retain personal information in our files despite your request to delete it in order to cooperate with law enforcement personnel or third parties to investigate possible crimes or resolve disputes; to enforce our User Agreement; to evaluate technical difficulties with the site; and for other internal purposes. Because we follow standard back-up procedures to assure the integrity of our computer and database systems, and due to technical constraints, it may not be technically possible to completely remove all of your personal information from our files. 

**OUR KIDS POLICY**

Our site is for Formula One fans and car enthusiasts in general. Although the contents of our site are accessible to a range of audiences, the vast majority of our users are adults. Children under the age of 13 are not eligible to participate in chat rooms, to buy products online, or to enter any contests or promotions. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 and no information should be submitted to or posted at F1i.com's Web sites by guests under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian.

Users between the ages of 13 to 17 are required to provide the e-mail address of a parent or guardian and a notification message is sent to the parent or guardian identifying the information supplied at registration and allowing the parent or guardian to be aware of and participate in the user's online experience.

**USER AGREEMENT**

YOUR USE OF THIS WEB SITE CONSTITUTES YOUR EXPRESS CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS POLICY AND INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE INTO OUR USER AGREEMENT. THIS POLICY IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE. ANY MATERIAL CHANGES IN THE MANNER IN WHICH WE HANDLE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, HOWEVER, WILL BE POSTED HERE FOR 30 DAYS BEFORE THEY GO INTO EFFECT. CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE REVISED TERMS. 

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

F1i.com  
93 Crosby St. - 2

ND floor  
New York, NY 10012  
(212) 965-8484 

Please direct all inquiries about this policy to [info@F1i.com](mailto:info@F1i.com).
